<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="legal_screen_title">Legal &amp; About</string>
    <string name="legal_settings_entry_title">Legal &amp; About</string>
    <string name="legal_settings_entry_subtitle">Privacy, license, contact, and sources</string>

    <string name="legal_section_about_title">About this app</string>
    <string name="legal_section_about_body">Baro shows a single world significance score (1–10) and up to three top events — a calm alternative to endless news feeds.\n\nThe Android app only downloads a public JSON file over HTTPS. It does not run AI on your device and does not collect personal data.\n\nChoose a country lens in Settings. Scores reflect how world events may affect daily life in that country (Poland, Romania, Portugal, Ukraine, or United States). The app does not use your GPS location.</string>

    <string name="legal_section_privacy_title">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="legal_section_privacy_body">Baro does not collect, store, or share any personal data. The app requires no sign-in and does not use location, contacts, or advertising identifiers.\n\nNetwork: the app downloads a public result file over HTTPS from a trusted host (e.g. barometer_pl.json depending on your selected country lens). No information about you or your device is sent with that request.\n\nLocal storage: your settings (country lens, notification threshold, notifications on/off) and the last fetched result are stored on your device only (DataStore Preferences).\n\nPermissions:\n• Internet — to fetch a public barometer file for your selected country lens (e.g. barometer_pl.json)\n• Notifications (Android 13+) — alerts are generated locally on your phone; we do not use server push notifications.\n\nThird-party content: headlines are processed on a server from public RSS feeds (see “Content &amp; sources”). Summaries are generated automatically and may contain errors.\n\nChildren: this app is not directed at children under 13.\n\nChanges: we may update this policy; the in-app text reflects the version shipped with the app.</string>

    <string name="legal_section_license_title">Open source license</string>
    <string name="legal_section_license_body">Baro (Android app) is open source under the MIT License.\n\nYou may use, copy, modify, and distribute the app source code according to the license terms, provided the copyright notice is included.\n\nSee the LICENSE file in the project repository for the full legal text.</string>
    <string name="legal_view_source_github">View source on GitHub</string>

    <string name="legal_section_sources_title">Content &amp; sources</string>
    <string name="legal_section_sources_body">Scores and summaries are produced automatically from public RSS headlines, including:\n\n• BBC News\n• Al Jazeera\n• The Guardian (World)\n\nBaro is not affiliated with these publishers. Short summaries in the app are AI-generated for informational purposes only — not a substitute for original reporting. Expand an event on the home screen to see which sources contributed to that item.\n\nRSS content remains subject to each publisher’s terms. Do not redistribute full articles from within this app.</string>

    <string name="legal_section_contact_title">Contact</string>
    <string name="legal_section_contact_developer">Developer: pb2112</string>
    <string name="legal_section_contact_email">Email: pb2112@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="legal_section_contact_github">GitHub: @pb2112-netizen</string>

    <string name="legal_version_format">Baro v%1$s (%2$d)</string>

    <string name="legal_privacy_online_copy">Online copy</string>

    <string name="legal_cd_open_github">Open GitHub repository</string>
    <string name="legal_cd_open_privacy_policy">Open privacy policy in browser</string>
    <string name="legal_cd_send_email">Send email to developer</string>
</resources>
